(Howard:)So you got any special plans
with your sister?
(Raj:)Oh, not really. Just hang out.
(Sheldon:)I always tell people,
"If you have only one day
(Sheldon:)in Los Angeles,
make it a train day."
(Raj:)Train day?
(Sheldon:)The fun starts with brunch
at Carney's in Studio City,
a hotdog stand in a
converted railroad dining car.
(Sheldon:)Next stop, Travel Town,
(Sheldon:)an outdoor museum featuring
43 railroad engines,
(Sheldon:)cars, and other rolling stock
from the 1880s to the 1930s.
And, finally, we're off to the
glitz and glamour of Hollywood,
for dinner at--that's right--
the Hollywood Carney's,
a hotdog stand in a different
converted railroad dining car.
(Raj:)I don't think
we're going to do that.
(Sheldon:)Well, then apparently
you hate fun.
(Leonard:)Priya's not back yet?
(Leonard:)Well, I guess
that's not unusual.